<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authorization on </title>
    <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v2/authorization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authorization on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v2/authorization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Design</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v2/authorization/design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v2/authorization/design/</guid>
      <description>Container Storage Modules (CSM) for Authorization is designed as a service mesh solution and consists of many internal components that work together in concert to achieve its overall functionality.
This document provides an overview of the major components, including how they fit together and pointers to implementation details.
If you are a developer who is new to CSM for Authorization and want to build a mental map of how it works, you&amp;rsquo;re in the right place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uninstallation</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v2/authorization/uninstallation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v2/authorization/uninstallation/</guid>
      <description>The CSM Authorization RPM will be deprecated in a future release. It is highly recommended that you use CSM Authorization Helm deployment or CSM Operator going forward.
This section outlines the uninstallation steps for Container Storage Modules (CSM) for Authorization.
Uninstalling the RPM To uninstall the rpm package on the system, you must first uninstall the K3s SELinux package if SELinux is enabled. To uninstall the K3s SELinux package, run:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v2/authorization/upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v2/authorization/upgrade/</guid>
      <description>The CSM Authorization RPM will be deprecated in a future release. It is highly recommended that you use CSM Authorization Helm deployment or CSM Operator going forward.
This section outlines the upgrade steps for Container Storage Modules (CSM) for Authorization. The upgrade of CSM for Authorization is handled in 2 parts:
Upgrading the CSM for Authorization proxy server Upgrading the Dell CSI drivers with CSM for Authorization enabled Upgrading CSM for Authorization proxy server Obtain the latest single binary installer RPM by following one of our two options here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLI</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v2/authorization/cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v2/authorization/cli/</guid>
      <description>The CSM Authorization karavictl CLI is no longer actively maintained or supported. It will be deprecated in CSM 2.0.
karavictl is a command-line interface (CLI) used to interact with and manage your Container Storage Modules (CSM) Authorization deployment. This document outlines all karavictl commands, their intended use, options that can be provided to alter their execution, and expected output from those commands.
If you feel that something is unclear or missing in this document, please open up an issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v2/authorization/troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v2/authorization/troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>The CSM Authorization RPM will be deprecated in a future release. It is highly recommended that you use CSM Authorization Helm deployment or CSM Operator going forward.
RPM Deployment The Failure of Building an Authorization RPM Running karavictl tenant commands result in an HTTP 504 error Installation fails to install policies After installation, the create-pvc Pod is in an Error state Intermittent 401 issues with generated token The Failure of Building an Authorization RPM This response occurs when running &amp;lsquo;make rpm&amp;rsquo; without the proper permissions or correct pathing of the Authorization repository.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
