<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Metrics on </title>
    <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/observability/metrics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Metrics on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/observability/metrics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PowerFlex Metrics</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/observability/metrics/powerflex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/observability/metrics/powerflex/</guid>
      <description>This section outlines the metrics collected by the Container Storage Modules (CSM) Observability module for PowerFlex. The Grafana reference dashboards for PowerFlex metrics can be uploaded to your Grafana instance.
I/O Performance Metrics Storage system I/O performance metrics (IOPS, bandwidth, latency) are available by default and broken down by export node and volume.
To disable these metrics, set the sdc_metrics_enabled field to false in helm/values.yaml.
The following I/O performance metrics are available from the OpenTelemetry collector endpoint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerMax Metrics</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/observability/metrics/powermax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/observability/metrics/powermax/</guid>
      <description>This section outlines the metrics collected by the Container Storage Modules (CSM) Observability module for PowerMax. The Grafana reference dashboards for PowerMax metrics can be uploaded to your Grafana instance.
Prerequisites Unisphere user credentials must have PERF_MONITOR permissions. Ensure time synchronization for Kubernetes cluster and PowerMax Unisphere by using Network Time Protocol (NTP). I/O Performance Metrics Storage system I/O performance metrics (IOPS, bandwidth, latency) are available by default and broken down by storage group and volume.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerScale Metrics</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/observability/metrics/powerscale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/observability/metrics/powerscale/</guid>
      <description>This section outlines the metrics collected by the Container Storage Modules (CSM) Observability module for PowerScale. The Grafana reference dashboards for PowerScale metrics can be uploaded to your Grafana instance.
I/O Performance Metrics Storage system I/O performance metrics (IOPS, bandwidth) are available by default and broken down by cluster and quota.
To disable these metrics, set the performanceMetricsEnabled field to false in helm/values.yaml.
The following I/O performance metrics are available from the OpenTelemetry collector endpoint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerStore Metrics</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/observability/metrics/powerstore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/observability/metrics/powerstore/</guid>
      <description>This section outlines the metrics collected by the Container Storage Modules (CSM) Observability module for PowerStore. The Grafana reference dashboards for PowerStore metrics can be uploaded to your Grafana instance.
I/O Performance Metrics Storage system I/O performance metrics (IOPS, bandwidth, latency) are available by default and broken down by export node and volume.
To disable these metrics, set the karaviMetricsPowerstore.volumeMetricsEnabled field to false in helm/values.yaml.
The following I/O performance metrics are available from the OpenTelemetry collector endpoint.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
