<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Migration on </title>
    <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v1/replication/migration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Migration on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v1/replication/migration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Between Storage Arrays</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v1/replication/migration/migrating-volumes-diff-array/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v1/replication/migration/migrating-volumes-diff-array/</guid>
      <description>User can migrate existing pre-provisioned volumes to another storage array by using the array migration feature.
NOTE: Currently only migration of standalone block volumes is supported.
Prerequisites This feature needs to be planned in a controlled host environment.
If the user have native multipathing, the user has to run multipath list commands on all nodes to ensure that there are no faulty paths on the host. If any faulty paths exist, the user has to flush the paths, and have a clean setup before migration is triggered using the following command:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between Storage classes</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v1/replication/migration/migrating-volumes-same-array/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v1/replication/migration/migrating-volumes-same-array/</guid>
      <description>You can migrate existing pre-provisioned volumes to another storage class by using volume migration feature.
Currently two versions of migration are supported:
To replicated storage class from NON replicated one. To NON replicated storage class from replicated one. Prerequisites Original volume is from the one of currently supported CSI drivers (see Support Matrix) Migrated sidecar is installed alongside with the driver, you can enable it in your myvalues.yaml file migration: enabled: true Support Matrix Migration Type PowerMax PowerStore PowerScale PowerFlex Unity NON_REPL_TO_REPL Yes No No No No REPL_TO_NON_REPL Yes No No No No Basic Usage To trigger migration procedure, you need to patch existing PersistentVolume with migration annotation (by default migration.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
