<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Replication on </title>
    <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Replication on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/installation/</guid>
      <description>The installation process consists of two steps:
Install Container Storage Modules (CSM) for Replication Controller Install CSI driver after enabling replication Before you begin Please read this document before proceeding with the installation. It provides detailed steps on how to set up communication between multiple clusters which will be required during or after the installation.
Install CSM Replication Controller You can use one of the following methods to install CSM Replication Controller:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConfigMap &amp; Secrets</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/configmap-secrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/configmap-secrets/</guid>
      <description>Communication between clusters Container Storage Modules (CSM) for Replication Controller requires access to remote clusters for replicating various objects. There are two ways to set up this communication:
Using Normal Kubernetes users Using ServiceAccount token You need to create secrets (using either of the two methods) in each cluster involved in replication and provide their references in ConfigMap objects which are used to configure the respective CSM Replication Controllers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installation using repctl</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/install-repctl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/install-repctl/</guid>
      <description>Install Replication Walkthrough NOTE: These steps should not be used when installing using Dell CSM Operator.
Set up repctl tool Before you begin, make sure you have the repctl tool available.
You can download a pre-built repctl binary from our Releases page.
wget https://github.com/dell/csm-replication/releases/download/v1.9.0/repctl-linux-amd64 mv repctl-linux-amd64 repctl chmod +x repctl Alternately, if you want to build the binary yourself, you can follow these steps:
git clone -b v1.9.0 https://github.com/dell/csm-replication.git cd csm-replication/repctl make build Installation steps NOTE: The repctl commands only have to be run from one Kubernetes cluster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installation using script</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/install-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/install-script/</guid>
      <description>Install Replication Walkthrough NOTE: These steps should be repeated on all Kubernetes clusters where you want to configure replication.
git clone -b v1.9.0 https://github.com/dell/csm-replication.git cd csm-replication kubectl create ns dell-replication-controller # Download and modify the default values.yaml file if you wish to customize your deployment in any way wget -O myvalues.yaml https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dell/helm-charts/csm-replication-1.9.0/charts/csm-replication/values.yaml bash scripts/install.sh --values ./myvalues.yaml Note: Current installation method allows you to specify custom &amp;lt;FQDN&amp;gt;:&amp;lt;IP&amp;gt; entries to be appended to controller&amp;rsquo;s /etc/hosts file.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storage Class</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/storageclasses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/storageclasses/</guid>
      <description>Replication Enabled Storage Classes In order to create replicated volumes &amp;amp; volume groups, you need to add some extra parameters to your storage class definition. These extra parameters generally carry the prefix replication.storage.dell.com to differentiate them from other provisioning parameters.
Replication enabled storage classes are always created in pairs within/across clusters and are generally mirrors of each other. Before provisioning replicated volumes, make sure that these pairs of storage classes are created properly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerFlex</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/powerflex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/powerflex/</guid>
      <description>Enabling Replication In CSI PowerFlex Container Storage Modules (CSM) Replication sidecar is a helper container that is installed alongside a CSI driver to facilitate replication functionality. Such CSI drivers must implement dell-csi-extensions calls.
CSI driver for Dell PowerFlex supports necessary extension calls from dell-csi-extensions. To be able to provision replicated volumes you would need to do the steps described in the following sections.
Before Installation On Storage Array Be sure to configure replication between multiple PowerFlex instances using instructions provided by PowerFlex storage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerMax</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/powermax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/powermax/</guid>
      <description>Enabling Replication In CSI PowerMax Container Storage Modules (CSM) Replication sidecar is a helper container that is installed alongside a CSI driver to facilitate replication functionality. Such CSI drivers must implement dell-csi-extensions calls.
CSI driver for Dell PowerMax supports necessary extension calls from dell-csi-extensions. To be able to provision replicated volumes you would need to do the steps described in the following sections.
Note: File Replication for PowerMax is currently not supported</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerScale</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/powerscale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/powerscale/</guid>
      <description>Enabling Replication in CSI PowerScale Container Storage Modules (CSM) Replication sidecar is a helper container that is installed alongside a CSI driver to facilitate replication functionality. Such CSI drivers must implement dell-csi-extensions calls.
CSI driver for Dell PowerScale supports necessary extension calls from dell-csi-extensions. To be able to provision replicated volumes you would need to do the steps described in the following sections.
Before Installation On Storage Array Ensure that SyncIQ service is enabled on both arrays, you can do that by navigating to SyncIQ section under Data protection tab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerStore</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/powerstore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/deployment/helm/modules/installation/replication/powerstore/</guid>
      <description>Enabling Replication In CSI PowerStore Container Storage Modules (CSM) Replication sidecar is a helper container that is installed alongside a CSI driver to facilitate replication functionality. Such CSI drivers must implement dell-csi-extensions calls.
CSI driver for Dell PowerStore supports necessary extension calls from dell-csi-extensions. To be able to provision replicated volumes you would need to do the steps described in the following sections.
Before Installation On Storage Array Be sure to configure replication between multiple PowerStore instances using instructions provided by PowerStore storage.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
