<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CSM Modules on </title>
    <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v3/deployment/csmoperator/modules/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CSM Modules on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v3/deployment/csmoperator/modules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Authorization</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v3/deployment/csmoperator/modules/authorization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v3/deployment/csmoperator/modules/authorization/</guid>
      <description>The CSM Authorization karavictl CLI is no longer actively maintained or supported. It will be deprecated in CSM 2.0.
Install CSM Authorization via Dell CSM Operator The CSM Authorization module for supported Dell CSI Drivers can be installed via the Dell CSM Operator. To deploy the Operator, follow the instructions available here.
Prerequisite Execute kubectl create namespace authorization to create the authorization namespace (if not already present). Note that the namespace can be any user-defined name, in this example, we assume that the namespace is &amp;lsquo;authorization&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Observability</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v3/deployment/csmoperator/modules/observability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v3/deployment/csmoperator/modules/observability/</guid>
      <description>The CSM Observability module for supported Dell CSI Drivers can be installed via the Dell CSM Operator. Dell CSM Operator will deploy CSM Observability, including topology service, Otel collector, and metrics services.
Prerequisites Create a namespace karavi kubectl create namespace karavi Enable Observability module and components in sample manifests. If cert-manager has already been installed, don&amp;rsquo;t enable it. Scenario 1: Deploy one supported CSI Driver and enable Observability module
If you enable metrics-powerscale or metrics-powerflex, must enable otel-collector as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Replication</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v3/deployment/csmoperator/modules/replication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v3/deployment/csmoperator/modules/replication/</guid>
      <description>The CSM Replication module for supported Dell CSI Drivers can be installed via the Dell CSM Operator. Dell CSM Operator will deploy the CSM Replication sidecar and the CSM Replication Controller Manager.
Prerequisites To configure Replication prior to installation via CSM Operator, you need:
a source cluster which is the main cluster a target cluster which will serve as the disaster recovery cluster NOTE: If using a single Kubernetes cluster in a stretched configuration, there will be only one cluster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resiliency</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v3/deployment/csmoperator/modules/resiliency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/v3/deployment/csmoperator/modules/resiliency/</guid>
      <description>The CSM Resiliency module for supported Dell CSI Drivers can be installed via the Dell CSM Operator. Dell CSM Operator will deploy CSM Resiliency sidecar.
Prerequisite When utilizing CSM for Resiliency module, it is crucial to note that it will solely act upon pods that have been assigned a designated label. This label must have both a key and a value that match what has been set in the resiliency module configuration.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
