<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Troubleshooting on </title>
    <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/csidriver/troubleshooting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Troubleshooting on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/csidriver/troubleshooting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PowerFlex</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/csidriver/troubleshooting/powerflex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/csidriver/troubleshooting/powerflex/</guid>
      <description>Symptoms Prevention, Resolution or Workaround After installation vxflexos-node pods are in an Init:CrashLoopBackOff state in OpenShift 4.16 with error message: Back-off restarting failed container sdc in pod vxflexos-node on non-supported kernel versions. Use SDC version 4.5.2.1 in OpenShift 4.16. The installation fails with the following error message: Node xxx does not have the SDC installed Install the PowerFlex SDC on listed nodes. The SDC must be installed on all the nodes that need to pull an image of the driver.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerMax</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/csidriver/troubleshooting/powermax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/csidriver/troubleshooting/powermax/</guid>
      <description>Symptoms Prevention, Resolution or Workaround kubectl describe pod powermax-controller-&amp;lt;xyz&amp;gt; –n &amp;lt;namespace&amp;gt; indicates that the driver image could not be loaded You may need to put an insecure-registries entry in /etc/docker/daemon.json or log in to the docker registry kubectl logs powermax-controller-&amp;lt;xyz&amp;gt; –n &amp;lt;namespace&amp;gt; driver logs show that the driver cannot authenticate Check your secret’s username and password kubectl logs powermax-controller-&amp;lt;xyz&amp;gt; –n &amp;lt;namespace&amp;gt; driver logs show that the driver failed to connect to the U4P because it could not verify the certificates Check the powermax-certs secret and ensure it is not empty or it has the valid certificates Driver install or upgrade fails because of an incompatible Kubernetes version, even though the version seems to be within the range of compatibility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerScale</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/csidriver/troubleshooting/powerscale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/csidriver/troubleshooting/powerscale/</guid>
      <description>Here are some installation failures that might be encountered and how to mitigate them.
Symptoms Prevention, Resolution or Workaround The kubectl logs isilon-controller-0 -n isilon -c driver logs shows the driver cannot authenticate Check your secret&amp;rsquo;s username and password for corresponding cluster The kubectl logs isilon-controller-0 -n isilon -c driver logs shows the driver failed to connect to the Isilon because it couldn&amp;rsquo;t verify the certificates Check the isilon-certs- secret and ensure it is not empty and it has the valid certificates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerStore</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/csidriver/troubleshooting/powerstore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/csidriver/troubleshooting/powerstore/</guid>
      <description>Symptoms Prevention, Resolution or Workaround When you run the command kubectl describe pods powerstore-controller-&amp;lt;suffix&amp;gt; –n csi-powerstore, the system indicates that the driver image could not be loaded. - If on Kubernetes, edit the daemon.json file found in the registry location and add { &amp;quot;insecure-registries&amp;quot; :[ &amp;quot;hostname.cloudapp.net:5000&amp;quot; ] } - If on OpenShift, run the command oc edit image.config.openshift.io/cluster and add registries to yaml file that is displayed when you run the command.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity XT</title>
      <link>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/csidriver/troubleshooting/unity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dell.github.io/csm-docs/docs/csidriver/troubleshooting/unity/</guid>
      <description>Symptoms Prevention, Resolution or Workaround When you run the command kubectl describe pods unity-controller-&amp;lt;suffix&amp;gt; –n unity, the system indicates that the driver image could not be loaded. You may need to put an insecure-registries entry in /etc/docker/daemon.json or login to the docker registry The kubectl logs -n unity unity-node-&amp;lt;suffix&amp;gt; driver logs show that the driver can&amp;rsquo;t connect to Unity XT - Authentication failure. Check if you have created a secret with correct credentials fsGroup specified in pod spec is not reflected in files or directories at mounted path of volume.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
